(gentle music)
(gentle rock music)
♪ How did you get here ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ I've tried that love
thing for the last time ♪
♪ My heart says no, no ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ But you came along and changed my mind ♪
♪ My mind, my mind ♪
♪ I've spent all my life ♪
♪ On a search to find ♪
♪ The love who'll stay for eternity ♪
♪ The heaven sent to fulfill my needs ♪
♪ But when I turn around ♪
♪ Again love has knocked me down ♪
♪ My heart got broken ♪
♪ Oh, it hurt so bad ♪
♪ I'm sad to say ♪
♪ Love wins again ♪
♪ So I placed my heart ♪
♪ Under lock and key ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ To take some time and take care of me ♪
♪ But I turn around and
you're standing here ♪
♪ How did you get here ♪
♪ Get here, get here ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ I've tried that love thing ♪
♪ For the last time ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ My heart says, no, no ♪
♪ My heart says ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ But you came along and changed my mind ♪
♪ My mind, my mind ♪
♪ This time I swear I'm through ♪
♪ But if only you knew ♪
♪ How many times I've said those words ♪
♪ Then fall again ♪
♪ When will I ever learn ♪
♪ Knowing these tears I cry ♪
♪ This lovely black butterfly ♪
♪ Must take a chance and spread my wings ♪
♪ Love can make you do some crazy things ♪
♪ So I placed my heart ♪
♪ Under lock and key ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ To take some time and take care of me ♪
♪ But I turn around and
you're standing here ♪
♪ How did you ♪
♪ Standing here ♪
♪ How did you get here ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ No, nobody ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Shouldn't nobody's ♪
♪ Supposed to be here ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody ♪
♪ Nobody ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ How did you get here ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I've tried that love thing ♪
♪ I've tried in ♪
♪ For the last time ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ My heart says no, no ♪
♪ My heart says no ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ But you came along ♪
♪ Came along ♪
♪ And changed my mind ♪
♪ And you changed ♪
♪ My mind ♪
♪ How did you get here ♪
♪ I'm not supposed to love ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ I'm not supposed to care anymore ♪
♪ I've tried that love
thing for the last time ♪
♪ My heart says ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no ♪